Arthur J. Pulos Papers
Arthur J. Pulos Papers
- Design practice/office records
  - Piper Aircraft Corporation
    - PI-41 1979 Registration numbers, 1977-78 (Box 8)
    - PI-42 1979 Custom color program, 1977-78 (Box 8)
    - PI-43 Cheyenne escutcheon program, 1978-79 (Box 8)
    - PI-44 1979 Aerostar, 1978; includes slides (Box 8)
    - PI-45 1979 Color selector program, 1978-79; includes photographs (Box 8)
    - PI-46 1979 Cheyenne display models, 1978; includes photographs (Box 9)
    - PI-47 1980 Exterior program, 1978-79; includes slides (Box 9)
    - PI-48 Cheyenne III display model, 1979 (Box 9)
    - PI-49 Cheyenne I & II display models, 1979-80 (Box 9)
    - PI-50 1981 Exterior program, 1979-80; includes slides (Box 9)
    - PI-51 Piper/Bangor Punta Corp. identity, 1980 (Box 9)
    - PI-52 Tomahawk program, 1980 (Box 9)
    - PI-53 PA-46 Display model, 1980 (Box 9)
    - PI-54 1982 Exterior program, 1980-81; includes slides (Box 9)
    - PI-55 1983 Exterior program, 1981-82; includes slides (Box 9)
    - PI-56 1984 Exterior program, 1983-84; includes photographs, slides (Box 9)
  - Porter Cable Division/Rockwell International
    - Porter cable/rockwell billing, 1958-69 (Box 10)
    - PO-Gen General consulting, 1958-69 (Box 10)
    - PO-4 Model 160 saw, 1958 (Box 10)
    - PO-7 Riding lawn mower, 1958-60; includes photographs, slides (Box 10)
    - PO-8 Escutcheon-1959 riding mower, 1958 (Box 10)
    - PO-8a Yardmaster logotype, 1958 (Box 10)
    - PO-9 Low cost edger/trimmer, 1958 (Box 10)
    - PO-10 Low cost tractor, 1958-60; includes photographs, slides (Box 10)
    - PO-11 Routo-jig, 1959-60 (Box 10)
    - PO-12 Low cost router, 1959-60; includes photographs (Box 10)
    - PO-13 Logo for 1960 mark 26, 1959 (Box 10)
    - PO-14 Nailer, 1959-60; includes photographs, slides (Box 10)
    - PO-15 Corporate identity program, 1960-61 (Box 10)
    - PO-16 Colors for #533 saw, 1959-60; includes slides (Box 10)
    - PO-17 Multi-saw redesign, 1959-60; includes slides (Box 10)
    - PO-18 Power block plane, 1960; includes photographs (Box 10)
    - PO-19 Golf cart, 1959 (Box 10)
    - PO-20 Rototiller, 1959-60 (Box 10)
    - PO-21 Router bank ring gauge, 1959-60 (Box 10)
    - PO-22 Home tool line, 1959-60; includes photographs, slides (Box 10)
    - PO-23 Boat, 1959-60; includes slides (Box 10)
    - PO-24 Mark 14 mower, 1960 (Box 10)
    - PO-25 Front end tiller, 1960 (Box 10)
    - PO-26 Snow blower, 1960 (Box 10)
    - PO-27 Left hand drive saw, 1960 (Box 10)
    - PO-28 Belt sander, 1960-61 (Box 10)
    - PO-29 R & M grinder, 1960 (Box 10)
    - PO-30 Model 100 router, 1960 (Box 10)
    - PO-31 Shear #544 and nibbler #545, 1960 (Box 10)
    - PO-32 Half pad orbital sander, 1960 (Box 10)
    - PO-33 7" Saw line, 1960-61; includes photographs (Box 10)
    - PO-35 Cord reel, 1960 (Box 10)
    - PO-36 Till drill, 1960 (Box 10)
    - PO-37 Tractor for montgomery ward, 1960 (Box 10)
    - PO-39 Rototiller markings, 1960 (Box 10)
    - PO-40 Low priced bayonet saw, 1960 (Box 10)
    - PO-41 Home tool line drill, 1960 (Box 10)
    - PO-42 Low cost saw, 1960 (Box 10)
    - PO-50 Employee activity room interior, 1960 (Box 10)
    - PO-51 Direct drive sander, 1960-63; includes photographs (Box 10)
    - PO-52 Engineering floor layout plans, 1960-61 (Box 10)
    - PO-54 Montgomery ward riding mower, 1961 (Box 10)
    - PO-55 Rototiller logo, 1961 (Box 10)
    - PO-56 Rockwell product markings, 1961 (Box 10)
    - PO-57 Montgomery ward belt sander, 1961 (Box 10)
    - PO-58 Sander nameplate, 1961 (Box 10)
    - PO-59 Low cost tool line, 1961 (Box 10)
    - PO-60 Specification plates, 1961 (Box 10)
    - PO-61 Sander pad nameplates, 1961 (Box 10)
    - PO-62 Double insulated deck scaler, 1961 (Box 10)
    - PO-63 6½" Saw markings, 1961 (Box 10)
    - PO-64 10" Saw restyling, 1961 (Box 10)
    - PO-65 Router motor housing, 1961 (Box 10)
    - PO-66 Portaband saw markings, 1961 (Box 10)
    - PO-67 Heavy duty drill markings, 1961 (Box 10)
    - PO-68 Nameplate markings, 1961 (Box 10)
    - PO-69 Compatability study-new tool line, 1961 (Box 10)
    - PO-70 Corporate markings and artwork, 1963-65; includes slides (Box 10)
    - PO-71 Double insulated tool line, 1961-62 (Box 10)
    - PO-72 Power block sander, 1962-63; includes photographs (Box 10)
    - PO-73 Veneer trimmer, 1962 (Box 10)
    - PO-74 Isometrics - drills, 1963 (Box 10)
    - PO-75 Revised power block plane, 1962 (Box 10)
    - PO-76 "B" line professional drills, 1963; includes slides (Box 10)
    - PO-77 "C" line drill, 1963-65; includes photographs, slides (Box 10)
    - PO-78 "D" line grinder, 1964-66; includes photographs (Box 10)
    - PO-79 1/3 Pad sander, 1963 (Box 10)
    - PO-80 Company entrance, 1963 (Box 10)
    - PO-81 Industrial bayonet saw, 1963-64 (Box 10)
    - PO-82 Lawn & garden tools, 1963 (Box 10)
    - PO-83 Green line promotion, 1964-65; includes photographs, slides (Box 10)
    - PO-85 Surface plane, 1964-65; includes photographs, slides (Box 10)
    - PO-86 Promotional belt sanders, 1964-65 (Box 10)
    - PO-87 Builder's jig saw, 1964-65; includes photographs (Box 10)
    - PO-88 Green line ½" promotional drill, 1964-65 (Box 10)
    - PO-89 Professional drill, 1964-67; includes photographs (Box 10)
    - PO-90 Industrial drill, 1964-65; includes photographs (Box 10)
    - PO-91 Promotional router, 1964-65; includes photographs (Box 10)
    - PO-92 Promotional circular saw, 1964-65; includes photographs, slides (Box 10)
    - PO-93 Contour belt sander, 1964-67; includes photographs (Box 10)
    - PO-94 "A" line project #9610, 1965; includes slides (Box 10)
    - PO-95 Promotional saber saw, 1965; includes photographs (Box 10)
    - PO-96 "C" grinder, 1965-67 (Box 10)
    - PO-97 ½" Impact wrench, 1965-67 (Box 10)
    - PO-98 5" W. D. saw, 1965-67 (Box 10)
    - PO-99 "D" size aerial grinder, 1966-67; includes photographs (Box 10)
    - PO-100 Color and finish studies, 1966-67 (Box 10)
    - PO-101 Over/under impact wrench, 1966 (Box 10)
    - PO-102 B-4 hammer, 1966-67 (Box 10)
    - PO-103 Telescoping guard control lever, 1966 (Box 10)
  - Porter Cable Division/Rockwell
    - Rockwell account records, 1969-74 (Box 11)
    - Rockwell accounts, photos, slides, 1975-76 (Box 12)
    - RO-Gen Rockwell general consulting, 1969-76 (Box 13)
    - RO-1 Delta radial arm saw review, 1963; includes slides (Box 13)
    - RO-2 12" Radial saw, 1963 (Box 13)
    - RO-3 Nameplates, 1963; includes slides (Box 13)
    - RO-4 Private brand radial arm saw, 1964 (Box 13)
    - RO-5 Drill press restyling program, 1964 (Box 13)
    - RO-6 Delta single arm saw, 1964 (Box 13)
    - RO-7 Private brand single arm saw, 1964; includes slides (Box 13)
    - RO-8 Compact line colors & styling, 1964; includes slides (Box 13)
    - RO-9 New line colors and styling, 1964 (Box 13)
    - RO-10 Plastic kits, 1964 (Box 13)
    - RO-11 Beaver jointer, 1964 (Box 13)
    - RO-12 Buckeye air tools-leveque sander, 1964-65; includes photographs (Box 13)
    - RO-13 Low cost stationary power tools, 1964-67; includes photographs, slides (Box 13)
    - RO-14 Color and finish study, 1964-67 (Box 13)
    - RO-15 Delta industrial stationary tools, 1964-65; includes photographs, slides (Box 13)
    - RO-16 4" and 6" jointers, 1965-66 (Box 13)
    - RO-17 Lathe colors and styling, 1965 (Box 13)
    - RO-18 Radial saw colors, 1965 (Box 13)
    - RO-19 Radial arm saw, horizontal mills, 1965 (Box 13)
    - RO-20 Beaver 10" T. A. saw, 1965 (Box 13)
    - RO-21 14" Radial saw blade guard, 1965 (Box 13)
    - RO-22 13" x 5" Planer, 1965-68; includes slides (Box 13)
    - RO-23 Motorized miter box, 1965-66; includes photographs (Box 13)
    - RO-24 Uniplane, 1965-67; includes photographs (Box 13)
    - RO-25 6" Beaver sander, 1965 (Box 13)
    - RO-26 15" Drill press, 1965; includes photographs (Box 13)
    - RO-27 ½" Impact wrench, 1965-66; includes photographs (Box 13)
    - RO-28 German low cost drills, 1965 (Box 13)
    - RO-29 Syderic stationary tools, 1965; includes slides (Box 13)
    - RO-30 9" T.A. saw for J.C. Penney, 1965-66 (Box 13)
    - RO-31 Steel stand-9" and 10" saws, 1965 (Box 13)
    - RO-32 Unisaw motor cover, 1964 (Box 13)
    - RO-33 Syderic paris sales office, 1965-66 (Box 13)
    - RO-34 Plus 10 handle, 1966 (Box 13)
    - RO-35 21" Drill press, 1966-68; includes photographs (Box 13)
    - RO-36 18" Planer, 1966 (Box 13)
    - RO-37 R. B. center point saw, 1966-67; includes slides (Box 13)
    - RO-38 Variable speed head vertical mill, 1966-67 (Box 13)
    - RO-39 Vacuum cleaner cover, 1966 (Box 13)
    - RO-40 Green line drill redesign, 1966-67; includes photographs (Box 13)
    - RO-41 Compact tool line, 1966-67 (Box 13)
    - RO-42 Air drill & screwdriver, 1966-67 (Box 13)
    - RO-43 Side handle drill, 1966-67 (Box 13)
    - RO-44 15" & 20" Band saws, 1966-67 (Box 13)
    - RO-45 Color standards program, 1966-67 (Box 13)
    - RO-46 Corporate marking standards, 1966-67 (Box 13)
    - RO-47 Corporate finishes standards, 1967 (Box 13)
    - RO-48 "A" Line builder's drill, 1967 (Box 13)
    - RO-49 Magnetronic industrial tools, 1967-70 (Box 13)
    - RO-50 Kit boxes, 1967-68 (Box 13)
    - RO-51 Low cost uniplane, 1967-68 (Box 13)
    - RO-52 Magnetronic motor study, 1967 (Box 13)
    - RO-53 Unisaw guard, 1967 (Box 13)
    - RO-54 "D" drill and power units, 1967; includes photographs (Box 13)
    - RO-55 New tool line color program, 1967 (Box 13)
    - RO-56 1" Square drive impact wrench, 1967 (Box 13)
    - RO-57 Junior grinder, 1967 (Box 13)
    - RO-58 Interior decorating, 1968; includes slides (Box 13)
    - RO-59 Magnetronic jig saw, 1967-69 (Box 13)
    - RO-60 Manual nailer, 1967 (Box 14)
    - RO-61 5HP magnetronic router, 1967-68 (Box 14)
    - RO-62 9" Builder's table saw, 1967 (Box 14)
    - RO-63 Magnetronic right angle drill, 1967 (Box 14)
    - RO-64 Green line jig saw, 1967 (Box 14)
    - RO-65 Green line sander, 1968 (Box 14)
    - RO-66 Magnetronic pistol grip drill, 1967-68 (Box 14)
    - RO-67 Duro belt & disc sander, 1967 (Box 14)
    - RO-68 Positive feed industrial tools, 1967 (Box 14)
    - RO-69 Oil hole drill press, 1967 (Box 14)
    - RO-70 Push button switch cover, 1967-70 (Box 14)
    - RO-71 Portaband redesign, 1967-69 (Box 14)
    - RO-72 Rotary hammer, 1966-70 (Box 14)
    - RO-73 Magnetronic line color & finish, 1967 (Box 14)
    - RO-74 Green line drill auxiliary handle, 1967 (Box 14)
    - RO-75 Graphics program, 1970-77; includes photographs, slides (Box 14)
    - RO-76 Power tool forecast, 1965-71; includes photographs, slides (Box 14)
    - RO-77 Model 75K kit box, 1967-68 (Box 14)
    - RO-78 "D" drill stand, 1967-68 (Box 14)
    - RO-79 Kango hammer, 1967-68 (Box 14)
    - RO-80 3 Speed drill, 1967-68 (Box 14)
    - RO-81 Solid state vertical mill, 1968 (Box 14)
    - RO-82 5 Gallon vacuum cleaner, 1968 (Box 14)
    - RO-83 Combin. disc and belt sander, 1968 (Box 14)
    - RO-84 6" Jointer, 1968 (Box 14)
    - RO-85 Oil hole drilling machine, 1968 (Box 14)
    - RO-86 Bandsaw blade, shaper/cutter pkg., 1968-69 (Box 14)
    - RO-87 Duro router/shaper, 1968-70 (Box 14)
    - RO-88 4½" Panel and trim saw, 1968-69 (Box 14)
    - RO-89 17" Drill press, 1968 (Box 14)
    - RO-90 15" Drill press, 1968 (Box 14)
    - RO-91 Comprehensive labeling system, 1968 (Box 14)
    - RO-92 Automotive drill line, 1968-71 (Box 14)
    - RO-93 Reversible 41F series, 1968-71 (Box 14)
    - RO-94 9" Single arm radial arm saw, 1968 (Box 14)
    - RO-95 Low cost porta band, 1969-70 (Box 14)
    - RO-96 6" x 12" Surface grinder, 1968-72 (Box 14)
    - RO-97 Over/under impact wrench, 1968-72; includes photographs (Box 14)
    - RO-98 "C" line stationary tool stand, 1968-72 (Box 14)
    - RO-99 Interiors, 1968-72 (Box 14)
    - RO-100 20" Drill press, 1969-70 (Box 14)
    - RO-101 Preliminary jackson green line, 1969 (Box 14)
    - RO-102 Power cabinet, 1969 (Box 14)
    - RO-103 Green line hedge trimmer, 1969; includes photographs, slides (Box 14)
    - RO-104 Low cost drill, 1969 (Box 14)
    - RO-105 Packaging identity manual, 1969 (Box 14)
    - RO-106 Green line jig saw, 1970; includes photographs, slides (Box 14)
    - RO-107 3/4" Posidrive air & electric tools, 1970 (Box 14)
    - RO-108 Tap gun, 1969-70 (Box 14)
    - RO-109 Quality level ident.-consumer tools, 1969-70 (Box 14)
    - RO-111 Edger/trimmer, 1969-71; includes slides (Box 14)
    - RO-112 Numerical control cabinet, 1969-71 (Box 14)
    - RO-113 Model 548 bayonet saw, 1969-70 (Box 14)
    - RO-114 New drill press study, 1969 (Box 14)
    - RO-115 Mini tool line revision, 1970 (Box 14)
    - RO-116 Graphics program, 1970 (Box 14)
    - RO-117 Circular saw, 1969-72; includes slides (Box 14)
    - RO-118 Demolition hammer, 1969-70 (Box 14)
    - RO-119 Kit box colors, 1969-70 (Box 14)
    - RO-120 ICON/boston, 1970-71; includes photographs, slides (Box 14)
    - RO-121 Grass trimmer, 1969-70 (Box 14)
    - RO-122 Consumer finishing sander, 1970-71 (Box 14)
    - RO-123 Saw fence handle, 1970 (Box 14)
    - RO-124 Sawmaster band saw, 1970; includes photographs (Box 14)
    - RO-125 Radial drill press markings, 1969-70 (Box 14)
    - RO-126 Builder's jig saw, 1970 (Box 14)
    - RO-127 New 20" drill press, 1970 (Box 14)
    - RO-128 Router (cancelled) (Box 14)
    - RO-129 M.A.T. redesign, 1970-71 (Box 14)
    - RO-130 High speed vertical grinder, 1971-72 (Box 14)
    - RO-131 11" Drill press, 1970-71 (Box 14)
    - RO-132 Battery-operated grass trimmer, 1970 (Box 14)
    - RO-133 24" Planer, 1970 (Box 14)
    - RO-134 16" Band saw, 1970 (Box 14)
    - RO-135 Circle "R" project, 1970 (Box 14)
    - RO-136 Horizontal band saw, 1970-71; includes photographs (Box 14)
    - RO-137 "D" line drill, 1970 (Box 14)
    - RO-138 EFI drilling machines, 1970-71 (Box 14)
    - RO-139 Corporate seal, 1970 (Box 14)
    - RO-140 Router line, 1972-75; includes photographs, slides (Box 14)
    - RO-141 Deluxe 10" radial arm saw, 1970-71 (Box 14)
    - RO-142 LAGUN vertical milling machine, 1970 (Box 14)
    - RO-143 Low cost air tools, 1970-71; includes photographs, slides (Box 14)
    - RO-144 Saw line redesign program, 1971 (Box 14)
    - RO-146 Future project study, 1969-71; includes slides (Box 14)
    - RO-147 B.A.P.T. color and markings, 1971; includes slides (Box 14)
    - RO-148 Screwdriver, 1971-72 (Box 14)
    - RO-149 Leaf shredder, 1971 (Box 14)
    - RO-150 5" & 6" Consumer bench grinders, 1971 (Box 14)
    - RO-151 1/4" and 3/8" Drills, 1971 (Box 14)
    - RO-152 Self-feeding drill, 1971 (Box 14)
    - RO-153 Builder's circular saw, 1971 (Box 14)
    - RO-154 Wrench and sander, 1971 (Box 14)
    - RO-155 Horizontal band saw, 1971-72; includes photographs (Box 14)
    - RO-156 Stationary power tool promotion, 1971 (Box 14)
    - RO-157 Flying chips program, 1971-72 (Box 14)
    - RO-158 8" Tilting arbor saw, 1971-72 (Box 14)
    - RO-159 Flight leader line, 1972 (Box 14)
    - RO-160 10" Contractor's T. A. S., 1972 (Box 14)
    - RO-161 Miter gauge (Box 14)
    - RO-162 Power feed attachment, 1972 (Box 14)
    - RO-163 New rockwell logo, 1972-75; includes slides (Box 14)
    - RO-164 Battery operated shrub trimmer, 1972; includes slides (Box 14)
    - RO-165 Consumer stationary line, 1972-73; includes slides (Box 14)
    - RO-166 Color and markings, 1972-73; includes slides (Box 14)
    - RO-167 Automotive line, 1972-73 (Box 14)
    - RO-168 Impact wrench, 1972 (Box 14)
    - RO-169 10" Band saw, 1972-73 (Box 14)
    - RO-170 2" Sander/7" grinder, 1972 (Box 14)
    - RO-171 10" Bandsaw, 1972 (Box 14)
    - RO-172 Radial arm saw, 1973; includes slides (Box 14)
    - RO-173 Pavement breaker, 1972 (Box 14)
    - RO-174 Montgomery ward line, 1972 (Box 14)
    - RO-175 2½" Sander/10" grinder, 1972 (Box 14)
    - RO-176 Low cost jig saw, 1972-73; includes photographs (Box 14)
    - RO-177 16" Vertical band saw, 1972-73 (Box 14)
    - RO-178 Low cost porta band, 1972 (Box 14)
    - RO-179 Interior/exterior, 1972-73 (Box 14)
    - RO-180 3/8" Palm grip impact tool, 1973 (Box 14)
    - RO-181 3/8" Pistol grip impact tool, 1973 (Box 14)
    - RO-182 Saw package, 1973 (Box 14)
    - RO-183 1/2" Impact tool, 1973; includes slides (Box 14)
    - RO-184 Low cost 4" jointer, 1973 (Box 14)
    - RO-185 Switch adapter, 1973 (Box 14)
    - RO-186 Private brand stationary tools, 1973 (Box 14)
    - RO-187 Low cost wood lathe, 1973 (Box 14)
    - RO-188 Low cost edger/trimmer, 1973; includes slides (Box 14)
    - RO-189 All purpose reciprocating saw, 1973 (Box 14)
    - RO-190 Builder's saw line, 1973; includes slides (Box 14)
    - RO-191 Retail low-cost saw line, 1973; includes slides (Box 14)
    - RO-192 10"/12" Radial arm saw, 1973-74; includes slides (Box 14)
    - RO-193 10" Low cost drill press, 1973; includes slides (Box 14)
    - RO-194 Packaging program, 1973-74; includes slides (Box 14)
    - RO-195 3/4" Impact wrench, 1973 (Box 14)
    - RO-196 Japanese air tool program, 1973 (Box 14)
    - RO-197 Drill line, 1973-74 (Box 14)
    - RO-198 Industrial accessory labels, 1974-75; includes slides (Box 14)
    - RO-199 Unicom systems calculator, 1974; includes slides (Box 14)
    - RO-200 Battery-operated drill, 1973-74 (Box 14)
    - RO-201 12" Consumer band saw, 1975 (Box 14)
    - RO-202 Industrial air tools color study, 1973 (Box 14)
    - RO-203 Business calculators, 1974 (Box 14)
    - RO-204 "C" line, 1973; includes slides (Box 14)
    - RO-205 Promotional tool line, 1973 (Box 14)
    - RO-206 Calculator line, 1974 (Box 14)
    - RO-207 Industrial vacuum cleaners, 1974; includes photographs, slides (Box 14)
    - RO-208 Wood lathe safety shield, 1974 (Box 14)
    - RO-209 Hammer drill housing, 1974 (Box 14)
    - RO-210 Speedmatic saw line, 1974 (Box 14)
    - RO-211 8" Table saw, 1974; includes slides (Box 14)
    - RO-212 Low cost motor miter box, 1974 (Box 14)
    - RO-213 Flight leader screwdriver, 1974 (Box 14)
    - RO-214 Marflow skin packs, 1974 (Box 14)
    - RO-215 "C" line graphics, 1974 (Box 14)
    - RO-216 Pistol grip graphics, 1974 (Box 14)
    - RO-217 Double insulated finishing sander, 1974-74 (Box 14)
    - RO-218 Drill press guards, 1975 (Box 14)
    - RO-219 Invicta tools - colr & markings, 1975 (Box 14)
    - RO-220 Automotive accessory packages, 1975; includes slides (Box 14)
    - RO-221 10" Radial arm saw, 1975-77; includes slides (Box 14)
    - RO-222 Screwdriver attachment, 1975 (Box 14)
    - RO-223 "D" handle, "B" size, 1975 (Box 14)
    - RO-224 Hole saw accessory packaging, 1975 (Box 14)
    - RO-225 Consumer stationary tools, 1975-76; includes photographs, slides (Box 14)
    - RO-226 Modular portable tool program, 1975; includes photographs (Box 14)
    - RO-227 Consumer paint gun, 1975-76 (Box 14)
    - RO-228 "Generac" color & markings, 1975 (Box 14)
    - RO-229 Stationary tool safety switch, 1975 (Box 14)
    - RO-230 6" Motorized jointer, 1976-77 (Box 14)
    - RO-231 12" Variable speed wood lathe, 1976; includes photographs (Box 14)
    - RO-232 Radial drill press, 1975-76 (Box 14)
    - RO-233 Impact wrench, 1976 (Box 14)
    - RO-234 Double insulated sander, 1976 (Box 14)
  - Precise Corporation
    - PR-1 Corporate identity program, 1975-76; includes photographs (Box 9)
  - Prosperity Company
    - PR-1 Coin-operated tumblers, 1961; includes slides (Box 9)
    - PR-2 House of kleen, 1961; includes photographs, slides (Box 9)
  - Rexair Company
    - RE-1 Vacuum cleaner (Box 9)
  - Ridge Tool Company
    - RI-1 Industrial portable power tools, 1977-78; includes slides (Box 9)
    - RI-2 Reciprocating saw model, 1977; includes slides (Box 9)
    - RI-3 Barrell grip jigsaw, 1977-79; includes slides (Box 9)
    - RI-4 Horizontal grinder, 1977-78; includes slides (Box 9)
    - RI-5 "D" handle drill, 1978; includes slides (Box 9)
    - RI-6 Circular saw, 1978-79; includes slides (Box 9)
    - RI-7 Hammer drill, 1978-79 (Box 9)
    - RI-8 Over/under drill, 1978-79; includes slides (Box 9)
    - RI-9 Band saws, 1979; includes slides (Box 9)
    - RI-10 Impact wrench, 1979 (Box 9)
    - RI-11 4½" grinder, 1978-79 (Box 9)
    - RI-101 Kollmann series, 1978-79; includes slides (Box 9)
    - RI-102 Portable electric drain cleaner, 1977-78 (Box 9)
    - RI-103 Drum type drain cleaner, 1978-81; includes photographs, slides (Box 9)
    - RI-103B Large drum drain cleaner, 1978 (Box 9)
    - RI-104 Product line appearance, 1978 (Box 9)
    - RI-105 Model 138 pipe cutter, 1978 (Box 9)
    - RI-106 K-50 drain cleaner, 1978-79; includes slides (Box 9)
    - RI-107 Kollmann 1500 family redesign, 1981 (Box 9)
    - RI-201 Pipe threading machine program, 1981-82; includes photographs, slides (Box 9)
  - Satellite Business Systems
    - SBS-10 Outside structure RF units, 1979; includes slides (Box 15)
    - SBS-20 Cabinetry, 1978-79; includes photographs, slides (Box 15)
    - SBS-30 Communications center, 1979 (Box 15)
    - SBS-40 Corporate identity program, 1978-80; includes photographs, slides (Box 15)
    - SBS-40-1 RF antenna markings, 1980; includes slides (Box 15)
    - SBS-40-2 House banner, 1980 (Box 15)
    - SBS-40-3 Color swatches, 1980 (Box 15)
    - SBS-40-4 Launch patches, 1980; includes slides (Box 15)
    - SBS-40-5 Launch decal, 1980; includes slides (Box 15)
    - SBS-40-6 Letterhead/calling card, 1981-82 (Box 15)
    - SBS-40-7 Equipment color, 1981-82 (Box 15)
    - SBS-40-8 Switched service/data port adaptors, 1981; includes slides (Box 15)
    - SBS-40-9 Company identity manual update, 1981; includes slides (Box 15)
    - SBS-50 General consulting services, 1980 (Box 15)
  - Skil Corporation
    - SK-1 Bench top tool program, 1982; includes slides (Box 15)
    - SK-2 Pistol grip drills, 1982; includes slides (Box 15)
    - SK-3 Weed eater, 1982; includes slides (Box 15)
  - Systems Planning Associates, Inc.
    - SP-1 Logotypes (Box 15)
  - Standard Shade Roller Company
    - ST-1 Decorative woven blinds, 1975; includes slides (Box 15)
  - Swingline Company
    - SW-1 Electric tacker, 1977 (Box 15)
    - SW-2 Private brand label maker, 1977 (Box 15)
    - SW-3 Collater, 1977; includes slides (Box 15)
    - SW-4 Slitter, 1977-78; includes slides (Box 15)
    - SW-5 Corporate identity program, 1977 (Box 15)
    - SW-6 Bindit project, 1977 (Box 15)
    - SW-7 Heavy duty stapler, 1977; includes slides (Box 15)
    - SW-8 #13 Stapler, 1977 (Box 15)
    - SW-9 Highly styled stapler, 1977-79; includes slides (Box 15)
    - SW-10 Plier desk model stapler, 1977-78 (Box 15)
    - SW-11 Showcase office, 1977 (Box 15)
    - SW-12 Kit design - electric tacker, 1977; includes slides (Box 15)
    - SW-13 Whammer kit design, 1977 (Box 15)
    - SW-14 Consumer line color concepts, 1977-78; includes slides (Box 15)
    - SW-15 Power gun 1000, 1977-78; includes slides (Box 15)
    - SW-16 Glue gun, 1977-78 (Box 15)
    - SW-17 Retail line, 1978 (Box 15)
    - SW-18 Filing systems, 1978; includes slides (Box 15)
    - SW-19 Electric stapler, 1978 (Box 15)
    - SW-20 Electric hole puncher, 1978-80 (Box 15)
    - SW-21 747 Stapler revision, 1978; includes slides (Box 15)
    - SW-22 Burster, 1978 (Box 15)
    - SW-23 Electric nailer colors, 1978 (Box 15)
    - SW-24 Hanging table, 1978 (Box 15)
    - SW-25 #113 and #13 staplers, 1979 (Box 15)
    - SW-26 Beauty lamp, 1979 (Box 15)
    - SW-27 Desk top continuous wire stapler, 1979 (Box 16)
    - SW-28 Revised color program, 1980 (Box 16)
    - SW-29 Cartridge stapler, 1980; includes slides (Box 16)
    - SW-30 Combination stapler, 1980 (Box 16)
    - SW-31 Stationary power tools, 1980; includes slides (Box 16)
    - SW-32 #444 (Base & cap), #747 base, 1980 (Box 16)
    - SW-33 All new 444, 1980; includes slides (Box 16)
    - SW-34 Omni desk electric stapler, 1980-81; includes slides (Box 16)
    - SW-35 Electric tacker, 1980; includes slides (Box 16)
    - SW-36 Omni electric staple gun, 1980 (Box 16)
    - SW-37 747 Color study (Box 16)